I wish...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I wish I had another chance.
A hospital?
My arm.
My leg's fine. too.
The hole in my chest
is also healed up.
So was that just a nightmare?
Oh. good.
Glad. you're already awake.
Who're you?
Hunter's Association Surveillance
Team manager. Jinchul Woo.
And I'm Taeshik Kang.
Okay. but...
what do you want with me?
Before that. let's get
your doctor in here.
What?
So you're telling me I was
unconscious for three whole days?
What about Joohee and Mister Song?
They're okay too. right?
Yes. but...
Chiyul Song lost an arm. which would
present a challenge for any hunter.
so he may retire.
Joohee Lee was deeply traumatized
and is receiving psychiatric care.
Given her condition. I suspect
she'll resign soon as well.
Of the thirteen hunters who raided
that dungeon. just six of you lived.
Only six.
Though we all know how dangerous hunting
is. it's rare to see such a tragic end.
And yet it gets even more unusual.
When the White Tiger Guild
arrived on the scene.
after being alerted by the survivors.
all they found was you.
The temple they'd been
told about had disappeared.
No trace of any statues either.
There was just
you collapsed on the ground.
No way.
It's quite hard to believe.
There were no inconsistencies
between their reports. however.
Not to mention we also recovered
the remains of the deceased.
Thus. we're much less
suspicious of your party.
Incidentally.
And this is just speculation.
of course. but...
Hunter Jinwoo Sung.
by chance. did you experience
a second awakening?
A second awakening?
Once a hunter's power manifests.
it doesn't change.
They get what they get.
Unless. that is. they have
a rare "second awakening".
It lets them exceed their limits
and rise to A or sometimes S-Rank.
Maybe I could. too!
This is a mana meter.
Place your hand on the stone. please.
If they really encountered
instakill-level magic beasts.
there's no way an average hunter would
have made it out of that situation alive.
And for those beasts to vanish
along with their dungeon suggests
the presence of an A
or even S-Rank hunter.
Making a second awakening
the most likely explanation.
Well. sir? What rank does
the mana meter say I am now?
Apologies. It would appear
that we were mistaken about you.
Huh?
Even E-Ranks typically
get higher than 70.
He's basically just a civilian.
The dungeon disappeared
and can't be explored again.
so how did he manage to survive?
Well. that sucks.
Went and got my hopes up.
I wonder. though.
Why'd they leave without
asking about this screen?
But. then again.
maybe they couldn't see it.
Guess it's not a touch panel.
This first popped up in that dungeon.
Jinah!
You have got to take
better care of yourself!
You know how worried
I've been about you?
I'm sorry.
Other hunters
are as healthy as can be.
But all of your raids
end up with you getting hurt!
My anxiety's through the roof!
To think I was prepared
to leave her behind.
What's with the smile?
This is serious because
next time something
like this happens
I'm dropping out of school.
I'm gonna find a job.
so you can quit yours!
Message officially received.
And speaking of.
do you see this thing?
-What thing?
-Uh. never mind.
Okay like. you know how video games
sometimes notify you about stuff?
Random tangent?
How would you open
one of those messages?
I'll go tell the doc
you need a neuro exam.
Come on. didn't you
used to be a gamer?
Yeah. I did. but don't all
unchecked messages go to an inbox?
Oh. right. Gotta open the inbox.
-Why suddenly bring up games?
-N-Not much to do in a hospital.
I remember this "Player" stuff
being mentioned before.
Well. you seem to be doing pretty okay.
so I'll be on my way. See you later.
Okay. Ready when you are. Song-yi.
"This system is designed to
assist the development of the Player.
Failure to comply with the
system may result in a penalty.
The rewards have been delivered."
I have no idea
what any of this means.
Huh? "Daily Quest:
Strength Training has arrived."
Uh. confirm.
Let's see. "Push-ups.
sit-ups. squats. running.
Failure to complete the daily quest
will result in an appropriate penalty."
What the...
Yeah. okay.
If this is a joke.
it's not a very good one.
Hospital patients don't exactly
have that energy to spare.
What in the world is going on?
Hello. Chairman Go.
We spoke with hunter Jinwoo Sung
at the hospital. and we were wrong.
I see.
We're lucky this incident
didn't result in a dungeon break.
But at the same time. it leaves
too many unanswered questions.
Agreed.
It's an unprecedented case.
to be sure.
No shortage of mysteries
when it comes to dungeons.
Let's mark this as a special case and enter
it into the databank. for further evaluation.
Yes. right away.
Gonna be a long day.
For the next B-Rank raid.
what would you say to taking on
an instructor role for us. Miss Cha?
An instructor? But why?
Well. this raid will serve as a test for
our new recruits. so I want you there.
If you're up to it.
I don't know how great
of a mentor I would be.
Fight as you usually do and
treat this raid as any other.
They can learn just
by seeing how you work.
Which is a true testament
to how talented you are.
Our guild is one of the five
largest in the country.
but we fall short
on an international scale.
Meaning that there's some
room for improvement.
Though I realize it sounds contrary.
our joint strength can increase
even if we as individuals can't.
Best to prepare.
No telling what's ahead.
Another gate.
Of course. it's in the
middle of the damn road.
I hope they can clear it soon.
Right? They should have
been here by now.
Wha..?! Is that an earthquake?
What the...
How'd I get here?
I'm dreaming. right?
I mean. I was just
in the hospital. and then.
Come on. You're kidding.
Wait.
Is something wrong?
Where'd the patient
from this room go?
How many of them are there?
Two more hours might
just kill me anyway!
-Any sign of him?
-No. None.
Maybe we just missed him
and he's back in his room now.
Let's check.
I seriously doubt he left
the hospital at this hour.
I can't keep on running forever!
A penalty.
Quest?
He's here!
Mister Sung! Are you all right?
Yep. Nearly healed now.
I should be able
to leave pretty soon.
I'm glad to hear it.
So where you gonna take me?
After all the stress you put me through.
you totally owe me. big time.
Yeah. yeah. Talk to you later.
All right. Time to go.
You want me to help with a raid?
Yeah.
A D-Rank gate appeared on a road in
Hop-jung. and all the guilds are tied up
with other obligations at the moment.
But it's fine if you'd rather not.
What you went through was horrible.
and that's totally understandable.
-I'm so sorry.
-Nah. don't apologize.
Oh. that reminds me.
I heard Hunter Sung
woke up and is doing great.
Jinwoo is doing okay?
He lived after everything.
That's wonderful!
-Look. there he goes again.
-Sheesh.
He's been running laps every
day since he first woke up.
But his leg...
I know hunters recover a lot faster
than normal people. but still...
He says he's trying
to get back into shape.
I've told him to take it easy.
but does he listen?
Acts like he was never injured.
Such a handful.
In the four days since I
regained consciousness.
I've figured out a few things.
To start. these screens
are not hallucinations.
When I complete the daily quest.
I receive three types of rewards.
Full recovery activate.
And just like that.
my fatigue is gone.
I also get ability points.
They boost my stats and I can
divide them up however I want.
so I've been beefing up my strength.
My power grows with each upgrade.
I can literally feel
the difference in my muscles.
Oh. yeah. and I've got these
skill and inventory screens. too.
As weird as the world's become.
mine somehow got even weirder.
Really it's like a game!
Oh. um...
And my final daily quest reward:
the random loot box.
What will it be today?
Ooh.
Figured it'd be more
bandages. pens.
or other useless stuff
like I've been getting.
An "instance dungeon"?
What is that?
Well. based on everything else. it's
sure to help me get stronger somehow.
And now a report on
today's gate conditions.
New D-Rank gates have appeared
at these locations. as you can see.
And the C-Rank gates in the
Upper East and Midtown areas
are currently being neutralized.
The B-Rank gate that popped up in
the wharf district is yet to be dealt with.
The Hunters Guild
is scheduled to raid it
within the next few days.
but steer clear until they do.
Avoiding the traffic caused by the gates
will save you both frustration and time.
Now for more detailed information
let's take a look at a couple of graphs.
As you'll note. we've had
some big dips and spikes.
but nothing abnormal to report.
Mom!
-Mom. you've gotta wake up!
-What's wrong with her?
I-I don't know.
She's not responding at all!
Eternal Sleep Disease?
Yes. "Final Rest" is
another term for it.
An illness that came into existence
with the appearance of the gates.
It affects one in every
ten thousand people or so.
It's not proven yet. but it's theorized
the cause is incessant exposure to mana.
Until we know more. life support is
the best modern medicine can offer her.
Let's see some hustle!
Put your back into it!
Right!
Congratulations.
You're qualified to be
a hunter. Mister Sung.
We look forward to seeing
what you're capable of.
See? This is it!
Now we can pay for Mom's treatment!
But it's dangerous.
I'll be okay.
You have my word on that!
The heck are you doing?
Go park it in a corner
somewhere and don't move!
Psh. Damned E-Rank.
slowing us down.
And for the record. the only ones who
get a cut are the ones who put in work!
Yeah. of course. Sorry. I suck.
I'll put my ability points
into strength.
Got all my gear ready.
Did everything
that needed to be done.
And hey. I'm the king
of running away.
If it gets as bad as last time.
I'll bolt out of there.
Huh.
Hey! Wait!
Why's the exit blocked off here?
I get it.
I stepped into a different dimension.
So. instance dungeons
aren't like the regular kind.
I bet they're closer to red gates.
though it's not like
I've been in one to compare.
Man. what a mess. Great.
so much for my exit strategy.
I was really counting on that. too.
A what stone?
So then. if I don't clear the dungeon.
I'll stay trapped in here.
All E-Rank beasts
wipe the floor with me.
but I'm supposed
to solo this whole thing.
Awesome.
With no help from anyone else.
can I really beat a boss?
I guess it's time to find out.
Okay. All my confidence is gone.
Three on one? Right off the bat?
I got one.
I...
I'm stronger now.
A wolf.
Much more challenging.
It's tougher than the goblins.
I can sense it.
My legs won't move!
Why?
Am I that afraid?
I thought I was over what happened.
No!
I don't have a healer.
So no second chances.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm